RG 030, Council of Defense
Connecticut State Library
- Series 1. General
  - 1. Classified file, 1917-1919
    - Historical Records Department (Box 79)
      - Z368.2: Giddings, H.A. - Letter re Life Insurance for those in Military Service (Box 79)
      - Z368.9: War Risk Insurance - Separation Allowances, Dependents, claims for pay, etc. Circular Letters and other Data (Box 80)
      - Z368.9: Field Investigations for Bureau of war Risk Insurance (Box 80)
      - Z368.91: Soldiers’ and Sailors’ Commission (Box 80)
      - Z381.1: Chambers of Commerce (Box 80)
      - Z381.06: Chambers of Commerce Meetings (Box 80)
      - Z381.12: Mr. Maddock’s Circular Letters to officials of Connecticut Chamber of Commerce (Box 80)
      - Z382: [Proclamation by Pres. of US - “Exports (Imports) in time of War”] (Box 80)
      - Z383: Mail for Soldiers - How to Address Letters, Postage Rates - Postal Service Personal Shipments (Box 81)
      - Z383.1: Franking Privilege (Box 81)
      - Z383.2: Letter to Manufacturers Enclosing Scovill Bulletin - Also Replies, 1917 November 6 (Box 81)
      - Z383.2: Correspondence Between Connecticut Council and the Manufacturers of Connecticut re Method Employed for Writing Letters to Employees in service - Replies to Letter Sent Aug. 1917 (Box 81)
      - Z383.3: How to send food or letters to prisoners of war in Germany (Box 81)
      - Z383.4: [Christmas Packages for Soldiers] (Box 81)
      - Z383.5: [Rural Delivery Service at Cheshire] (Box 81)
      - Z383.6: [Monthly Reports of State Board of Examiners of Barbers] (Box 81)
      - Z390: [War Trophies to Decorate Village Greens] (Box 81)
      - Z393: [Press Release re wearing of armbands to memorialize the War Dead] (Box 81)
      - Z620: Public Improvements (Box 81)
    - Non-War Construction (Box 81)
      - Z621: Record Book of Non-War Construction Applications, Compiled by Miss Ferguson (Box 81)
      - Z621: Building Construction - General Material (Box 81)
      - Z621.01: Non-war Construction - Personnel Local Districts (Box 81)
      - Z621.02: Building Construction - Press Material (Box 81)
      - Z621.03: State Office to Local Administrators - Circular Letters (Box 81)
      - Z621.03: Circular Messages to Local Administrators (Box 82)
      - Z621.041: Other Circular Letters (Box 82)
      - --------: [Survey of war plants, non-war plants, plus Highway Map of Connecticut] (Box 82)
      - Z621.0411: Letters Giving of Contractors and Lumber Dealers in Connecticut (Box 82)
      - Z621.042: Circular of Other States (Box 82)
    - Correspondence with Connecticut Districts (Box 82)
      - Z621.05a: Ansonia District (Box 82)
      - Z621.05b1: Bridgeport Applications (Box 82)
      - Z621.05b1: Bridgeport District (Box 83)
      - Z621.05b2: Bristol District (Box 83)
      - Z621.05d1: Danbury District (Box 83)
      - Z621.05d2: Derby District (Box 83)
      - Z621.05e: East Hartford District (Box 83)
      - Z621.05h: Hartford District (Box 83)
      - Z621.05h: Hartford Applications (Box 83)
      - Z621.05m: Manchester District (Box 83)
      - Z621.05m5: Meriden District (Box 83)
      - Z621.05m3: Middletown District (Box 83)
      - Z621.05n: New Britain District (Box 83)
      - Z621.05n3: New Haven District (Box 83)
      - Z621.05n3: New Haven Applications (Box 83)
      - Z621.05n5: New London District (Box 84)
      - Z621.05n7: Norfolk District (Box 84)
      - Z621.05n9: Norwalk District (Box 84)
      - Z621.05n11: Norwich District (Box 84)
      - Z621.05p: Putnam District (Box 84)
      - Z621.05r: Rockville District (Box 84)
      - Z621.053: Stanford District (Box 84)
      - Z621.05t: Thomaston District (Box 84)
      - Z621.05t2: Torrington District (Box 84)
      - Z621.05w: Wallingford District (Box 84)
      - Z621.05w3: Waterbury District (Box 84)
      - Z621.05w3: Waterbury Applications (Box 85)
      - Z625.05w4: Westbrook District (Box 85)
      - Z621.05w5: Willimantic District (Box 85)
      - Z621.05w7: Windsor District (Box 85)
      - Z621.05w9: Winsted District (Box 85)
      - Z621.06: Washington Correspondence (Box 85)
        - Richard L. Humphries, War Industries Board, Building Material Section (Box 85)
        - Labor Division (Hugh Frayne) (Box 85)
        - Edwin B. Parker - War Industries Board, Priorities Comm. (Box 85)
        - Other than Preceding folders. (Box 85)
        - With War Industries Board (H.R. Mc Lennan, etc.) (Box 85)
        - Housing Corporation (Box 85)
        - War Industries Board (B.M. Baruch Chairman) (Box 85)
        - Council of National Defense (Box 85)
      - Z621.07: Permits Pending, Washington (Box 85)
      - Z621.071: Applications Referred to S.P. Bush of War Industries Board (Box 86)
      - Z621.072: War Resources Committee, Connecticut (Box 86)
      - Z621.073: Permits Pending with Bradford D. Pierce - also Correspondence (Box 86)
      - Z621.074: Bridgeport Sub - Regional Chairman, C. E. Bilton (Box 86)
      - Z621.074: Hartford Sub - Regional Chairmen, R. H. Schutz (Box 86)
      - Z621.074: New Haven Sub - Regional Chairmen, I.N. Ullman (Box 86)
      - Z621.074: New London and Windham Counties, Sub - Regional Chairman (Box 86)
      - Z621.08: Correspondence other than Washington, or Outside of Districts (Box 86)
      - Z621.08: Mr. Ferguson’s Personal File (Box 86)
      - Z621.081: Mailing Room Instructions, Requisitions, etc. (Box 86)
      - Z621.09: Reports of Local Administrators and of State Chairmen (Box 86)
      - Z621.1: Building of New Advertising Signs (Box 86)
      - Z621.3: Highway Construction Work (Box 86)
      - Z621.3: Connecticut Highway Commissioners, Correspondence (Box 86)
      - Z623.1: War Industries Board, Rulings re Special Articles (Box 86)
      - Z623.11: Shoe Prices, Shoe Dealers in Connecticut (Box 86)
      - Z623.2: [Clipping re War Resources Committee] (Box 86)
      - Z623.3: [Government Notice re Local War Industries Committee] (Box 86)
      - Z626: [Letter from Charles H. Owen re: Plea to Publicize the Need for Inventive People with Ideas] (Box 86)
      - Z627: Water Waste (Box 86)
      - Z627.4: Correspondence with G.H. Gilpatrick, F.A. Mazzur Co., Westinghouse Electric & Mfg. Co. and Mr. Porter of Council of National Defense, re Putnam Electric Motor Proposition, 1917 December-1918 January (Box 86)
      - Z634.91: Need of Walnut Wood (Box 86)
      - Z640: Lunch Room (Box 86)
      - Z655: [Foreign Language Printers] (Box 86)
      - Z800: [Well Known Authors] (Box 86)
      - Z912.4: [Literary Digest with Latest War Maps] (Box 86)
      - Z912.76: Map of Hartford (Box 86)
      - Z920: [Resume of Tell A Turner, Resolution re O.S. Freeman, Satire of Kaiser] (Box 86)
      - Z620c: [Miss Margaret T. Corwin] (Box 86)
      - Z920g: [Press Release re: Major Howard A. Giddings, Governor Holcombe Message to the Troops, Food Situation in England, George C. Grawford, Annual Meeting of the National Association of State Librarians] (Box 86)
      - Z920ro: Resolutions re Theodore Roosevelt (Box 86)
      - Z920s: Press Release re Speeches by Julius G. Stremlan of Connecticut Council of Defense (Box 86)
      - Z920w: Correspondence re Judge Wheeler’s War Rally Speech (Box 86)
      - Z921: [Photographs of: Gen. G.M. Cole, Hon. Homer S. Cummings, Woodrow Wilson, R.H.M. Robinson of Bridgeport] (Box 87)
      - Z929.6: [Meaning of Army Ribbons] (Box 87)
      - Z929.7: Flag (Box 87)
      - Z929.8: Service Flags, Mother’s Emblems, etc. (Box 87)
      - Z930: Trophies From Battlefields for War Bureau (Box 87)
      - Z930: War Trophies (Box 87)
  - 2. Index to classified file, 1917-1919
    Alphabetical card index to Item 1 above. Includes references also to other series, some unidentified or lost.
    - A - Cop (Box 409)
    - Cor - K (Box 410)
    - L - Ra (Box 411)
    - Re - Z (Box 412)
  - 3. Correspondence with Council of Defense offices, 1917-1919
    Some of the material is indexed in item 2 above.
    - Council of National Defense, Washington (Box 88-89)
    - Council of Defense (Correspondence with the State Council and its Committees)
      - Americanization - Education (Box 90)
      - Finance - Food Supply (Box 91)
      - Food Supply - Publicity (Box 92)
      - Publicity - War Savings (Box 93)
      - Women's Committee - Women's Activities (Box 94)
    - Circular letters to local agencies (Box 94)
    - Circular letters to county committees (Box 95)
    - Town War Bureaus
      - Andover - Canterbury (Box 96)
      - Canton - Greenwich (Box 97)
      - Griswold - Middlefield (Box 98)
      - Middletown - New Haven (Box 99)
      - New Haven - Pomfret (Box 100)
      - Portland - Torrington (Box 101)
      - Trumbull - Woodstock (Box 102)
    - Other state councils, city councils, and county councils (Box 103)
    - Town and county bulletins and reports (Box 104-106)
  - 4. Miscellaneous correspondence, 1917-1919
    Arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent (either individuals or agencies, e.g. Council of Defense (Washington), Connecticut State, etc.)
    - A - As (Box 107)
    - At - Bi (Box 108)
    - Bl - Bro (Box 109)
    - By - Cha (Box 110)
    - Cha - Cl (Box 111)
    - Co - Conn. State Librarian (Box 112)
    - Conn. State T - Dl (Box 113)
    - Do - Fe (Box 114)
    - Fi - Gay (Box 115)
    - Ge - Hal (Box 116)
    - Ham - Int (Box 117)
    - Io - La (Box 119)
    - Mar - Na (Box 120)
    - Ne - Newspapers (Box 121)
    - Newspapers - Noo (Box 122)
    - Nor - Per (Box 123)
    - Ph - Red (Box 124)
    - Red - Sc (Box 125)
    - Se - Ste (Box 126)
    - Ste - U.S. Employment Service (Box 127)
    - U.S. Entomology Bureau - U.S. House (Box 128)
    - U.S. House - Wes (Box 129)
    - Wh - Z (Box 130)
  - 5. Reference file, 1917-1919
    Copies of bulletins, releases, posters, pamphlets and other publications of Connecticut and United States agencies, institutions and businesses pertaining to the war effort.
    Arranged roughly alphabetical by subject of publishing agency. At the end are Committee on Public Information ("Creel Committee") publications: Official Bulletin; War Information Series, "Red, white and blue series". An incomplete list of folder titles is in the first box.
    - Agriculture - General (Box 131)
    - Agriculture - US Department of (Box 131)
      - Bees (Box 131)
        - Diseases (Box 131)
        - Protection (Box 131)
      - Cotton (Box 131)
        - Diseases (Box 131)
        - General (Box 131)
      - Dairy (Box 131)
        - General (Box 131)
        - Milk (Box 131)
        - Cheese (Box 131)
        - Herds (Box 131)
      - Draft (Box 131)
      - Farming (Box 131)
        - General (Box 131)
        - Farm Labor (Box 131)
        - Cost of Producing Farm Products (Box 131)
        - Preparations for Farm Lands (Box 131)
      - Fruits (Box 131)
        - Nuts (Box 131)
      - Grains (Box 131)
        - [General] (Box 131)
        - Corn (Box 131)
        - Wheat (Box 131)
      - Insects (Box 131)
      - Markets (Box 131)
      - Poultry (Box 131)
        - General (Box 131)
        - Eggs (Box 131)
      - Seeds (Box 131)
        - General (Box 131)
      - Vegetable (Box 131)
        - General (Box 131)
      - Game Regulations (Box 131)
      - Lumber (Box 131)
      - Cattle Diseases (Box 131)
        - Shipment of Stock (Box 131)
        - Stockyard Regulations (Box 131)
      - Beans (Box 131)
        - Food for Cattle (Box 131)
      - Sheep (Box 131)
        - [General] (Box 131)
        - Sheep Wool (Box 131)
      - Weekly News Letter (Box 132)
    - Americanization (Box 132)
      - Address by Theodore Roosevelt (Box 132)
      - “Be a Truth Teller” - Americanization Section of the Council of National Defense (Box 132)
      - Americanization Insurance Policy - national Americanization Comm.. (Box 132)
      - Americanization Day - Fourth of July - US Bureau of Education (Box 132)
      - “What Women’s Organizations can do” - US Bureau of Education (Box 132)
      - “Americanize the Immigrant” - American Book Co. (Box 132)
      - Americanization in (Box 132)
        - Delaware - Delaware council of Defense (Box 132)
        - New Orleans, La. - Americanization Day (Box 132)
        - Pennsylvania - Penn. Council of Nat Defense (Box 132)
        - Cleveland chamber of Commerce Americanization Work (Box 132)
        - Sharon, Pa - “The Americanizer” - Valley Americanization Comm. (Box 132)
        - New York - National security League - Americanization War Work (Box 132)
        - Hartford, Conn. - Americanization Inaugural message - Marcus H. Holcomb (Box 132)
        - Americanizing a City - Detroit Board of Commerce and Education (Box 132)
        - Plan of Factory Co-operation - Americanization Comm. Detroit Board Commerce (Box 132)
        - Committee on Public Safety - New Hampshire Comm. on Americanization (Box 132)
        - Ohio State Council of Defense (Box 132)
        - New York - Americanization Program, National Comm. (Box 133)
        - Cleveland - Slovaks of, Cleveland Comm. (Box 133)
        - Cleveland - Americanization Program (Box 133)
        - Delaware - Americanization Program (Box 133)
        - Americanization Program - California Comm. of immigration and housing (Box 133)
        - Hartford - ‘Understand, Sympathize, Assist” Mayors Americanization Comm. (Box 133)
        - New Britain, Conn. - American Ideals (Box 133)
        - “War Facts on Americanization” - Conn. State Council of Defense (Box 133)
        - New Hampshire Americanization Comm. (Box 133)
      - “US immigration Service Bulletin” - US Department of Labor (Box 133)
      - Bulletin of the Board of Education, Department of university Extension (Box 133)
      - “Americanization Bulletin” - Department of Interior (Box 133)
      - “To Americans” - American League Citizenship (Box 133)
      - War Facts on Americanization - National Committee of One Hundred (Box 133)
      - “Americanizing Industrial Workers” - Manufacturer’s Record (Box 133)
      - Industrial Americanization Organization Chart (Box 133)
      - The Americanization of Our Foreign Born - Columbia Graphone Manufacturing Co.. (Box 133)
      - “America Most Favored Nation” by Rev. George Pentecost. (Box 133)
    - Babies: “The Well Baby Primer” by Elizabeth Memorial Fund (Box 133)
    - Birds (Box 133)
    - Boys - on farms - Penna. Council of Defense (Box 133)
      - “Boys Life” (Box 133)
      - “Scouting” (Box 133)
    - Bench and Board - by Pratt & Whitney, Hartford (Box 133)
    - Building After The War - US Department of Labor (Box 133)
    - Bulletins (Box 133)
      - Charity organization, New York (Box 133)
      - Colorado Fuel and Iron Co. (Box 133)
      - Conn. Temperature Union (Box 133)
      - General Chemical Bulletin (Box 133)
      - Bulletin to the School - University of the State of New York (Box 133)
      - “The Bulletin” - New York State Industrial Commission (Box 133)
      - “Business Bulletin” - Minneapolis Public Library (Box 133)
      - “Connecticut bulletin” - Conn. State Council of Defense (Box 133)
      - Labor Market Bulletins (Box 133)
      - “Triangle News” (Box 133)
      - War Library Bulletin (Box 133)
      - “US Employment Service Bulletin” - US Service of the Department of Labor (Box 134)
      - “War Bulletins” - Conn. State Council of Defense (Box 134)
      - Chamber of Commerce of US of America (Box 134)
      - “Chicago Commerce” - Chicago Assoc. of Commerce (Box 134)
      - “The Detroiter” - Detroit Board of Commerce (Box 134)
      - Orders - Interstate Commerce Commission (Box 134)
      - San Francisco - Chamber of Commerce Activities (Box 134)
      - “For Waterbury” - Waterbury Chamber of Commerce (Box 134)
      - “Members Bulletin” - Minneapolis Civic and Commerce Assoc. (Box 134)
      - “News Bulletin” - Philadelphia Chamber of Commerce (Box 134)
      - “Outline Course in Citizenship” - US Dept. of Labor (Box 134)
      - Pamphlets - Citizenship (Box 134)
    - Catalogues - [Cutter Desk Co. Buffalo, NY] (Box 134)
      - Keystone Stereographs - Keystone View Co. (Box 134)
    - Community Survey Morgan Memorial Parish, Boston, and Treasurers Annual report 1918 (Box 134)
    - Councils of Defense - State (Box 134)
      - “Alabama Defense Record” (Box 134)
      - “Arizona Service Bulletin” (Box 134)
      - Colorado - Use of the German League of America (Box 134)
      - Connecticut - “Hail France” (Box 134)
        - Statement of New Haven War Bureau (Box 134)
        - Liberty Songs (Box 134)
        - ”Why We Are At War With Germany” (Box 134)
      - Idaho - Official Press Bulletins (Box 134)
      - Illinois (Box 134)
        - “State Council News” (Box 134)
        - Bulletin No 34A: “War History Comm.” (Box 134)
      - Iowa - ”A Day of Judgment” (Box 134)
      - Minnesota (Box 134)
        - America (Box 134)
        - “Minnesota in the War” (Box 134)
      - “Missouri on Guard” (Box 135)
      - Montana - Orders (2 folders) (Box 135)
      - “Ohio in the War” (Box 135)
      - Oklahoma (Box 135)
      - “South Dakota on Duty” (Box 135)
      - Utah (Box 135)
      - Wisconsin - “Forward” (Box 135)
      - Wyoming (Box 135)
      - Alabama - Pamphlets (Box 135)
      - Arizona - Posters (Box 135)
      - Illinois - Publicity Dept. (Box 135)
      - Iowa - Circulars (Box 135)
    - Council of National Defense (Box 135)
      - “National Defense” (Box 135)
      - “News Letter” - Women’s Division (Box 135)
      - Bulletin (Box 135)
      - Information Circulars - Field Division (Box 135)
    - Conference of Community Forces and Reconstruction - Community Councils of National Defense (Box 135)
    - Department of the Interior (Box 135)
    - Draft (Box 135)
    - Editorial - “The Chicago Tribune” (Box 135)
    - Education (Box 135)
      - Bureau of Education - Dept. of the Interior (Box 135)
      - “School Life: - Dept. of Interior, Bureau of Education (Box 135)
      - Price List Government Publications, Superintendent of Documents, Washington (Box 135)
      - List - Industrial Plants Offering English for Foreigners (Box 135)
      - Industrial Plants and Education of their Employees (Box 135)
      - “Vocational Education” - Federal Board of Vocational Education (2 folders) (Box 135)
      - Report on Evening Schools - [Conn.] State Board of Education (Box 135)
      - Short Unit Courses - Board of Education of the City of New York (Box 135)
      - “Democracy’s Educational Problem” - National Security League, New York (Box 135)
      - Pennsylvania State Education Assn. - Program, 1918 (Box 135)
      - “Industrial Education” - National Association of Manufacturers (Box 135)
      - A National program for Education - National Education Association, Washington (Box 135)
      - “The Vocational Summary” - Federal Board for Vocational Education (Box 136)
      - Vocational School, New London (Box 136)
    - Employment (Box 136)
      - “Administration of Public Employment Bureaus” - Public Employment Bureau, new York (Box 136)
      - Employment Rules - Industrial Commission of Wisconsin (Box 136)
    - Food (Box 136)
      - US Food Administration - Washington (Box 136)
        - “Official Statement” (Box 136)
        - Conservation Notes (Box 136)
      - US Dept.. of Agriculture (Box 136)
        - Canning (Box 136)
        - Sugar (Box 136)
    - Fuel - US Fuel Administration, Washington. (Box 136)
      - Fuel Publication (Box 136)
      - Fuel Facts (Box 136)
      - General (Box 136)
      - Clay and Lime (Box 136)
      - Coal General (Box 136)
      - Coal Prices (Box 136)
      - Coal Saving (Box 136)
      - Anthracite Coal Prices (Box 136)
      - Anthracite - General (Box 136)
      - Mine and Miners (Box 136)
      - Bituminous Coal - General (Box 137)
      - Bituminous Coal - Prices (Box 137)
      - Charcoal (Box 137)
      - Coke - General (Box 137)
      - Coke - Prices (Box 137)
      - Electricity (Box 137)
      - Oils (Box 137)
      - Gasoline (Box 137)
      - Non-Use of Motor Vehicles (Box 137)
      - Gasoline Savings (Box 137)
      - Petroleum (Box 137)
      - Natural Gas (Box 137)
      - Wood General (Box 137)
    - Girls (Box 137)
      - Campfire Girls (Box 137)
      - Girl Scout Organization Literature (Box 137)
      - “The Rally” - Scouting Magazine for the American Girl” (Box 137)
      - “Wohelo” - Magazine for the Camp Fire Girls (Box 137)
    - Health (Box 137)
      - Public Health Nurse (Box 137)
      - “Philosophy of Health” by J.H. Tilden, M.D., Denver, Colorado (Box 137)
      - “National Effectiveness and Health Insurance” (Box 137)
      - US Public Health Service (Box 137)
        - “Keep Them Fit” (Box 137)
        - “Social Hygiene Monthly” (Box 137)
        - Spanish Influenza - Health Reports (Box 137)
        - Malaria - Health Reports (Box 137)
        - Venereal Disease - Health Reports (Box 137)
        - Posters - Influenza (Box 137)
        - Monthly List Publications (Box 137)
        - “Unregulated Cheap Lodging Houses” - Civic League of St. Louis (Box 137)
    - Immigrants (Box 138)
      - Housing Pamphlet - Commission on Immigration and housing of California (Box 138)
      - Prospectus of the Lowell Normal Method Course for Teachers of Immigrants in Evening Classes (Box 138)
      - Prince List naturalization Publication, etc. (Box 138)
      - “Who is Your Neighbor?” Mass. Bureau of Immigration (Box 138)
      - North America Civic league for Immigration - Federal Bureau of Distribution (Box 138)
      - Educational Facilities for Assimilation (Box 138)
      - Lectures and Instructions for Immigrant Education H.H. Wheaton, Yale School of Religion (Box 138)
      - City’s Responsibility to Immigrant - Bureau of Education, Dept. of Interior (Box 138)
      - Courses for the Immigrant (Box 138)
      - “How we Receive th Immigrant” - Rev. C.L. Mc Kee, United Presbyterian Church, Pittsburg, Pa. (Box 138)
      - Immigrant Reports - US Bureau of Education (Box 138)
      - Outline of Education of Adult Immigrants (Box 138)
      - US Bureau of Education and the Immigrant (Box 138)
      - Immigrant Women (Box 138)
      - “Know Your Enemy” Committee (Box 138)
    - Labor (Box 138)
      - US Department of Labor (Box 138)
        - “Children’s Year” (Box 138)
        - General (Box 138)
        - Bulletin No. 9 (Box 138)
        - Pamphlets (Box 138)
      - Chamber of Commerce of US (Box 138)
        - Engineering Methods Must Replace Paternalism in the Hanling of Labor (Box 138)
        - Draft Report of Committee on Labor Exchanges (Box 138)
        - Actual Account of What We Have Done to Reduce labor Turnover (Box 138)
    - Legislation (Box 138)
      - Acts - Legislation (Box 138)
      - Bills - Miscellaneous, House of representatives and Senate (Box 138)
      - Bills - Dept. of Interior (Box 138)
      - “Labor Laws in War Time” - American Assoc. for Labor Legislation (Box 138)
      - “American labor Legislation on Review” - American Assoc. for labor Legislation (Box 138)
      - Laws of Conn. Relating Bakeshops, Elevators, factories and Factory Inspection (Box 138)
      - Laws Relating to Local and State Fire Marshals - [Conn.] State Police Dept. (Box 138)
      - Executive Proclamations and War Legislation Commonwealth on Massachusetts (Box 138)
      - Documents on American Oriental Relations - to the President and Congress of US by Federal Council of Churches of Christ. (Box 138)
    - Liberty Chrouses and Community Singing - Council of National Defense (Box 138)
    - List - Employers and Industrial Men Interested in Americanization (Box 138)
    - List - Manufacturer’s Assn. Officers, Directors, etc. (Box 138)
    - Magazines (Box 138)
      - “America” - Catholic Review of the Week (Box 138)
      - “Literary Digest” (Box 138)
    - National Americanization Committee - “Why Factory Classes Pay” (Box 138)
    - National Committee of Patriotic Societies (Box 138)
    - National League for Women’s Service (Box 138)